

#### **CONTACT**

Mobile No. 009647507654818. Email: <a href="mailto:fatimahalwan3@gmail.com">fatimahalwan3@gmail.com</a>. Linkedin: <a href="www.linkedin.com/in/Fatima">www.linkedin.com/in/Fatima</a> H. Alwan Hussain.

# **NATIONALITY**

Iragi

## **BIRTH DATE**

May 28<sup>th</sup>, 1979

## **MARITAL STATUS**

Single

### **ADRESS**

Erbil / Mamustayan – Zanko

#### **EDUCATION**

Bachelor of Banking and Financial Sciences Dijla College - Private University Erbil 2013 Excellent Degree.

#### **SKILLS**

#### Languages:

-Arabic: Native Speaker.

-English: Very Good (reading & writing),

Good (speaking).

-Kurdish: Good (writing).

## Computing:

Good knowledge of using Microsoft Office: (Word, Excel, Power Point, Outlook), Email and Internet.

# **FATIMAH HUSSEIN ALWAN**

#### **PROFILE**

Hard working individual having Bachelor Degree in Banking and Financial Sciences with 10 years' experience in Banking. I would like to have the opportunity to make a strong contribution to the company's goals while continuing developing my own professional skills and career.

#### **WORK EXPERIENCE**

I worked in the Kurdistan International Bank for Investment and Development for the period from 4<sup>th</sup> Dec. 2006 until 30<sup>th</sup> June 2017, where I held the following positions:
-Secretary as writer and observer degree for the period from 4<sup>th</sup> Dec. 2006 until 8<sup>th</sup> Oct. 2013.

- Auditor in Control and Internal Audit Department for the period from 8<sup>th</sup> Oct. 2013 until 17<sup>th</sup> July 2014.
- Secretary in the General Counsel Office for the period from  $17^{th}$  July 2014 until July 2016.
- Observer in Anti Money Laundering Unit using (iMAL Banking System) from July 2016 until 30<sup>th</sup> June 2017.

# **COURSES & CERTIFICATES**

- ( Course in Banking Accounting and Course in Letters of Guarantee LG) in Kurdistan International Bank for Investment and Development / Erbil.
- Course in Banking Accounting in Finance and Banking Academy at the University of Kurdistan Hawler UKH for the period  $4^{\rm th}$  to 8th May 2014.
- Training Course in Accounting on the Electronic
   Accounting System (Al Mizan.Net for Accounting and
   Warehouse Inventory) established by the World Gate Serve for Accounting Services in Erbil from 18<sup>th</sup> Jan. to 18<sup>th</sup> Feb
   2018.
- Training Course in Ticketing, Hotel Reservations, Insurance and Visa from 1<sup>st</sup> to 29<sup>th</sup> April 2018.